caressskinwearcollection.com 2009-11-16

# Unilever Privacy Policy

|  | 

Unilever United States, Inc. is a member of the Unilever U.S. group of companies ("Unilever"). 

Unilever cares about your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of Personal Information, that is collected by Unilever from consumers and how we use and protect it. This Policy also tells you what to do if you do not want your Personal Information used for marketing purposes, and how you can change information you have already provided to us. This Policy applies to consumer-directed websites which link to this policy, including the ones listed here, and to Unilever's collection of data through printed promotional materials such as sweepstakes entry forms, coupons or other mail-in offers and telephone calls to Unilever's consumer services department. It does not apply to banners, sweepstakes or promotions sponsored by third parties in which Unilever participates. 

  * Your Consent to This Privacy Policy
  * Collection of Personal Information
  * How We Use Your Information
  * Other Information We May Collect
  * Privacy of Children
  * Security of Information
  * Changes in Our Policy
  * Who to Contact

|  | 

* * *

| 

####   Your Consent to This Privacy Policy  
  
---|---|---  
  
By providing Unilever with Personal Information, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted here. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not provide any Personal Information.

If you choose not to provide Personal Information, you may not be able to do certain things, like access particular areas of our websites, enter sweepstakes or contests, request samples, or send us e-mail. 

| 

* * *

| 

####   Collection of Personal Information  
  
---|---|---  
  
As used in this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means personally identifiable information such as your name, street address, telephone number, credit card information, screen name and email address.

When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of your Personal Information (see Who to Contact). 

We may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party (e.g., a website might allow you to send an electronic "post card" to a friend, in which case we will need that person's name and e-mail address). Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (e.g., to mail the post card) and we will not contact the third party again unless and until the third party contacts us. 

| 

* * *

| 

####   How We Use Your Information  
  
---|---|---  
  
When you supply us with your Personal Information we will use it for the express purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to enter you in a sweepstakes or to send you a sample). It may also be used by the brand responsible for the website or promotion, as well as by our other brands, to contact you regarding other products and services which may be of interest to you (including those we may offer jointly with other companies). For more information about Unilever and its brands, see About Unilever. At any time, however, you may opt out of such contact. (See Who to Contact)

At times we may retain third parties to analyze data we collect, including Personal Information, to help us improve our products and our web sites. In addition, if you order a product or service from us, we may provide Personal Information to suppliers and other third parties to enable delivery of such product or service. These third parties, including suppliers, are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any other way. Unilever does not sell Personal Information.

We may supplement the information that you provide to us with other information that we receive from third parties. We do this for marketing purposes in order to provide the most appropriate products and services to meet your needs.

We may also transfer, sell or assign your Personal Information to any entity to which we divest all or a portion of our business (for example, in connection with our sale of a brand), to the extent that you provided such information to the specific portion of our business (or brand) that is being divested, or otherwise in connection with a merger, consolidation, change in control, reorganization or liquidation of all or a portion of our business. 

Finally, please note that we will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order. 

| 

* * *

| 

####   Other Information We May Collect Online  
  
---|---|---  
  
Other information that we may collect online, via Unilever websites, e-mail promotions and banners, for example, is described in this section.

You may have heard of "cookies," which are files or pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Unilever may use cookies to collect other information during your visit to our web site, such as the particular site areas you visit and the products or services you buy through our web site. We collect this information to better tailor our site and our products to your interests and needs. Cookies may also be used to help speed up your future activities at our sites. For example, a site can recognize that you have provided Personal Information to us and refrain from requesting the same information a second time. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Refusal of cookies at the site you entered may result in an inability to visit certain areas of the site or to receive personalized information when you visit the site. 

In addition, we are constantly trying to improve how we promote our web sites. To help us do this, we may measure the effectiveness of our web presence by determining what you clicked on to get to our site. 

Site measurement statistics may be used to personalize your web site experience, as well as to evaluate – anonymously and in the aggregate – statistics about usage of the web site. Information about your computer, such as your IP address (a number assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Internet), the type of Internet browser you are using and the type of computer operating system you are using may also be collected and linked to your Personal Information. This is to ensure that our web sites present the best web experience for visitors, and that they are an effective information resource. 

Finally, some of the pages you visit may use pixel tags (also called clear gifs) to collect information about your navigation on our websites. This information is used to evaluate and enhance how the websites function.

| 

* * *

| 

####   Privacy of Children Online  
  
---|---|---  
  
Unilever is committed to protecting the online privacy of children and making the Internet safe for our users. The statements in this Policy generally about our collection and use of Personal Information also apply to our treatment of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, with the added protection of the special rules that follow. We encourage parents of children under 13 to regularly check and monitor their children's use of e-mail and other activities on line.

Unilever does not collect personal information from children under 13, except from time to time at certain sites that are directed to children, such as popsicle.com. Unilever handles this information in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA):

  * If your child provides us with online contact information (e.g., an e-mail address) solely so that we may respond more than once to a specific request (e.g., sending an on-line newsletter) and for no other purpose, then we will notify you via e-mail that this information has been provided to us. You have the right, as will be outlined in our notification and as set forth below (see Who to Contact), to ask that we not use your child's online contact information for this purpose. 

  * Before your child provides us with Personal Information beyond online contact information (e.g., a street address, phone number, etc.), or if we wish to use Personal Information for purposes other than responding more than once to a specific request, then we will contact you by e-mail and will require your signed permission, sent by real world mail, before we collect and use such information. 

  * If the information provided by your child is online contact information only (e.g., an e-mail address), and it is to be used to respond on a one-time basis to a specific request (e.g., to answer a question about one of our products), and thereafter it is deleted from our records, then we will not notify you.

| 

* * *

| 

####   Security of Information  
  
---|---|---  
  
We take reasonable precautions to keep your Personal Information secure. All personally identifiable information is subject to restricted access to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse.

| 

* * *

| 

####   Changes in Our Policy  
  
---|---|---  
  
Unilever reserves the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at our discretion. We will post any new policy here and we encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.

| 

* * *

| 

####   Who to Contact  
  
---|---|---  
  
Please write to us at [privacy.policy@unilever.com](mailto:privacy.policy@unilever.com) or at Unilever Consumer Services, 920 Sylvan Avenue, 2nd Floor, Englewood Cliffs, NJ 07632 or call us at 1-866-204-9750 if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or to report any violations of the Privacy Policy. We will respond to you within 24 to 48 hours in most cases. For other requests, please choose among the following options: 

> If you **don't want to be contacted** in the future or would like us to **correct or update your Personal Information** in our records, please click the appropriate button below:

  |   | 

Unilever will take reasonable steps to comply with the foregoing requests. 

Again, Unilever is committed to protecting your privacy. Please do not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy. 

|  | 

* * *

| 

####   About Unilever  
  
---|---|---  
  
Unilever is one of the world's largest consumer products companies, marketing a wide range of foods, home and personal care products. Our purpose is to meet the everyday needs of people everywhere.

Unilever's major products in the United States, are: Bertolli olive oil; Bertolli premium pasta sauces, olive oils and frozen dinners; Boursin cheeses; Degree, Dove - antiperspirants, deodorants and toiletries; Dove facial, skin and hair care products; Hellmann’s and Take Control spreads and dressings; Imperial, Promise, Country Crock, and "I Can't Believe It's Not Butter!", and spreads and sprays; Klondike, Popsicle and Breyers ice cream products; Knorr; Lever 2000, Dove, Caress, and Pears personal wash products; Lipton brewed teas and ready-to-drink tea based beverages, soups, recipe products and side dishes; Lipton BRISK ready-to-drink tea based beverages; Pond's facial and skin care products; Q-tips cotton swabs and cotton balls; Ragu pasta and pizza sauces; Rave hair care products; Slim-Fast shakes and bars; Suave; Sunsilk; Vaseline and Caress skin care products; Wish-Bone salad dressings.

Unilever websites to which this Policy applies, include:   [Axe](http://www.theaxeeffect.com/);  [Bertolli](http://www.villabertolli.com/);  [Best Foods](http://www.bestfoods.com/);  [Breyers](http://www.breyers.com/);  [Brummel and Brown](http://www.brummelandbrown.com/);  [Caress](http://www.caressskin.com/);  [Country Crock](http://www.countrycrock.com/);  [Degree](http://www.degreedeodorant.com/index.html);  [Dove](http://www.dove.com/);  [Hellmann's](http://www.mayo.com/);  ["I Can't Believe It's Not Butter!"](http://www.tasteyoulove.com/);  [Knorr](http://www.us.knorr.com/);  [Lever 2000](http://www.lever2000.com/);  [Lipton Brisk](http://www.liptonbrisk.com/);  [Lipton Recipe Secrets](http://www.recipesecrets.com/);  [Lipton Tea](http://www.liptont.com/);  [Making Life Better](http://www.makinglifebetter.com/);  [Ponds](http://www.ponds.com/);  [Popsicle](http://www.popsicle.com/);  [Promise](http://www.promisehealthyheart.com/);  [Ragu](http://www.eat.com/);  [Skippy](http://www.peanutbutter.com/);  [Slim-Fast](http://www.slimfast.com/);  [Suave](http://www.suave.com/);  [Sunsilk](http://www.sunsilk.us/);  [Take Control](http://www.takecontrol.com/);  [Vaseline](http://www.vaseline.com/);  [Wish-Bone](http://www.wish-bone.com/)

#### To return to the site you were visiting, press the back button on your browser.
